#### Contact

iryna.slynko@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/iryna-slynko (LinkedIn) github.com/Iryna-Slynko (Other) iryna-slynko.com/ (Personal)

# Top Skills

Software Coding Python Analytical Skills

# Languages

German (Professional Working)
Russian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Full Professional)
Ukrainian (Full Professional)

Advanced Google Analytics

### Certifications

Traffic Sign Classification Using Deep Learning in Python/Keras Python Data Structures Crash Course on Python by Google Data Collection and Processing with Python

# Iryna Slynko

Software Engineer Intern @ J.P. Morgan | Python | Java | JS, CSS, Node.js | SQL | Upskilling to Full-Stack Developer Dublin

# Summary

Grá for Technology, Coding and Solving Challenges. Final year computing student, specialising in Software Development / IT Management and on track for a 2:1. Ten months of experience in total as an Intern Software Engineer.

I have strong skills in Python, C# and SQL as well as learning Java, JavaScript, Node.js and Flask in current studies and upskilling to become a Full-Stack Software Engineer. I possess excellent communication, people and empathy skills with a Bachelors degree in Psychology. I am a great team player as well as initiative individual contributor.

My super skill? I love studying and improving, and inspire others to do so.

# Experience

JPMorgan Chase & Co.
Software Engineer Intern
June 2021 - Present (3 months)
Dublin, County Dublin, Ireland

Top 10 in 2021 EMEA Secure Coding Tournament;

Delivered features for the web app solution (Python, JavaScript, React,

Debugging, Unit Testing, Refactoring, Code Review, Jira, creating Wiki page)

Global Hackathon 2021 winner @JP Morgan Dublin (Java Spring);

as well as proposing improvement of onboarding, mentoring and feedback processes.

Verizon Media Associate Software Engineer March 2021 - June 2021 (4 months) Ireland

Trained in creating event-driven C# applications, OOP, IT Security and Software Design Principles. Shadowing Software Engineers on the Yahoo! ad

platform, participating in scrum meetings. Participated in diversity and inclusion events, eco initiatives.

#### Ardanis

Software Development Intern December 2020 - March 2021 (4 months)

Dublin City, County Dublin, Ireland

Web development (WordPress, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Git, Jira), client meeting participation, version control, Agile, demoing, code review and data migration project (Javascript, SOQL, Angular.js, Salesforce, Jira, Git).

CSinc (Computer Science Inclusive)
Software Development Contributor
June 2020 - August 2020 (3 months)
Ireland

Software Development Team @ http://csinc.ie/Home/Research - Developed Primary School Survey Scan System. Technology used: ASP.NET MVC, C#, MS Azure Computer Vision API(for handwritten text recognition), Unit testing, stories tracking, Git

### Accenture

App Content Analyst August 2019 - March 2020 (8 months) Co.Dublin

Most Valuable Player Award.

Supporting the client's app play store. Protecting and improving user experience of kids and families.

Contributed to adjusting the client's guidelines for the local market.

#### Freelance

**ESL Tutor** 

December 2005 - May 2015 (9 years 6 months)

IT Craft

**ESL Trainer** 

February 2009 - April 2013 (4 years 3 months)

Kharkiv Region, Ukraine

#### TEAM International

**Technical Recruiter** 

February 2007 - January 2009 (2 years)

H. S. Skovoroda Kharkiv National Pedagogical University Research And Teaching Assistant September 2005 - June 2007 (1 year 10 months)

# Education

Technological University Dublin

Bachelor of Science, Computing with IT Management · (September 2018 - November 2021)

### National College of Ireland

Higher Diploma in Science, Software Development · (January 2021 - April 2022)

V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University Bachelor's degree, Psychology (2008 - 2010)

H. S. Skovoroda National Pedagogic University

Master of Education, English Language and Literature (2006)